[Music]
verified Me by secure key Technologies
Incorporated is the new Canadian service
that helps you verify your identity
securely so you can get things done fast
online in person and on the phone start
by downloading the verified me app on
your mobile device here's how to sign up
with verified me when registering with
sunlife financial download the my
sunlife mobile app by visiting
sunlife.ca or my sunlife.ca and tap on
register you will be redirected Ed to
the sun life's registration website tap
register using verified me and you will
be taken to the verified me app if you
do not have the verified me app
installed on your mobile device you will
have the option to download it or open
verified me in your web browser you'll
see a splash screen that welcomes you to
the service tap sign up at the bottom of
the screen the app will display the
steps you must follow to become a
verified me user tap get started to
begin the registration process
the first step is to select a financial
institution with whom you have an active
and existing online banking relationship
the second step is to authenticate
yourself using your online banking
credentials with the financial
institution you've selected the verified
me app will take you to the login screen
of your financial institution's mobile
app or website where you will be asked
to sign in each time you use the
verified me service you will be asked to
authenticate yourself using your online
banking credentials with the financial
institution you've
selected once you have entered your
financial institution credentials you
may be prompted to enter additional
credential information for example a
security code sent to your device or
answer a
question once you have logged in you
will be presented with the information
your financial institution will make
available for you to share through the
verified Mi service with your consent
you will have an opportunity to review
your base profile consisting of your
name phone number address date of birth
email and agree to use this information
in association with your verified me
profile you'll then be taken back to the
verified Mi app to review and accept the
terms and conditions and privacy notice
by tapping agree these are the terms and
conditions that apply to your use of the
verified Mi service brought to you by
secure key
Technologies you will be prompted to
confirm that you have read and accepted
the verified me terms and conditions and
privacy notice a message will then
display confirming you have successfully
registered for the verified Mi service
you will then be taken to a screen to
review your base profile and will be
prompted to agree to share with sunlife
you can tap review for more details if
you wish when ready tap agree to share
your base profile with sunli to help
them verify your identity after tapping
agree verifi me will process your
request once the request has been
completed verified me will display a
success message informing you that base
profile information has been shared you
are now ready to complete your
registration with sunlife you will be
redirected to the sunlife website to
complete your registration and will
notice that your base profile
information has been
autofilled registration is almost
complete you can update your email
password and phone number you will also
be asked to select a verification
question from a list of drop- down
options once complete tap next that's it
you're now registered to access sunlife
online online thank you for watching
this video to learn more about verified
me visit www. verified. me